<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3 | Omid Taheri</title>
    <link>https://otaheri.github.io/publication-type/3/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://otaheri.github.io/publication-type/3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>3</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://otaheri.github.io/media/icon_hu9b7be29231a05e8610b49408e09cf277_125589_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>3</title>
      <link>https://otaheri.github.io/publication-type/3/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>GRIP: Generating Interaction Poses Conditioned on Object and Body Motion</title>
      <link>https://otaheri.github.io/publication/2023_grip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://otaheri.github.io/publication/2023_grip/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hands are dexterous and highly versatile manipulators,
that are central to how humans interact with objects and
their environment. Consequently, modeling realistic hand
object interactions, including the subtle motion of individual
fingers, is critical for applications in computer graphics,
computer vision, and mixed reality. To address this
challenge, we propose GRIP, a learning-based method that
synthesizes the motion of both left and right hands before,
during, and after interaction with objects. We leverage the
dynamics between the body and the object to extract two
types of novel temporal interaction cues. We then define a
two-stage inference pipeline in which GRIP first outputs the
consistent interaction motion by taking a new approach to
modeling motion temporal consistency in the latent space.
In the second stage, GRIP generates refined hand poses to
avoid finger-to-object penetrations. Both quantitative experiments
and perceptual studies demonstrate that GRIP
outperforms existing methods and generalizes to unseen objects
and motions. Furthermore, GRIP achieves real-time
performance with 45 fps hand pose prediction. Our models
and code will be available for research purposes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--
# Video

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/A7b8DYovDZY&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


# Data and Code

Please register and accept the License agreement on [GRAB](https://grab.is.tue.mpg.de) website in order to get access to the GRAB dataset. 



# Citation

```
@inproceedings{taheri2022goal,
    title = {{GOAL}: {G}enerating {4D} Whole-Body Motion for Hand-Object Grasping},
    author = {Taheri, Omid and Choutas, Vasileios and Black, Michael J. and Tzionas, Dimitrios},
    booktitle = {Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition ({CVPR})},
    year = {2022},
    url = {https://goal.is.tue.mpg.de}
}

@inproceedings{GRAB:2020,
    title = {{GRAB}: {A} Dataset of Whole-Body Human Grasping of Objects},
    author = {Taheri, Omid and Ghorbani, Nima and Black, Michael J. and Tzionas, Dimitrios},
    booktitle = {European Conference on Computer Vision ({ECCV})},
    year = {2020},
    url = {https://grab.is.tue.mpg.de}
}
```

--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Leg Motion Tracking by Fusing IMUs and RGB Camera Data Using Extended Kalman Filter</title>
      <link>https://otaheri.github.io/publication/2019_leg_imu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://otaheri.github.io/publication/2019_leg_imu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Human motion capture is frequently used to study rehabilitation and clinical problems, as well
as to provide realistic animation for the entertainment industry. IMU-based systems, as well as Markerbased
motion tracking systems, are most popular methods to track movement due to their low cost of
implementation and lightweight. This paper proposes a quaternion-based Extended Kalman filter
approach to recover the human leg segments motions with a set of IMU sensors data fused with
cameramarker system data. In this paper, an Extended Kalman Filter approach is developed to fuse the data of
two IMUs and one RGB camera for human leg motion tracking. Based on the complementary properties
of the inertial sensors and camera-marker system, in the introduced new measurement model, the
orientation data of the upper leg and the lower leg is updated through three measurement equations. The
positioning of the human body is made possible by the tracked position of the pelvis joint by the camera
marker system. A mathematical model has been utilized to estimate joints’ depth in 2D images. The
efficiency of the proposed algorithm is evaluated by an optical motion tracker system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--
# Video

&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://download.is.tue.mpg.de/arctic/video.mp4&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


# Data and Code

Please register and accept the License agreement on [GRAB](https://grab.is.tue.mpg.de) website in order to get access to the GRAB dataset. 



# Citation

```

```
--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
