<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>3 | Omid Taheri</title>
    <link>https://otaheri.github.io/publication-type/3/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://otaheri.github.io/publication-type/3/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>3</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://otaheri.github.io/media/icon_hu9b7be29231a05e8610b49408e09cf277_125589_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>3</title>
      <link>https://otaheri.github.io/publication-type/3/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human Leg Motion Tracking by Fusing IMUs and RGB Camera Data Using Extended Kalman Filter</title>
      <link>https://otaheri.github.io/publication/2019_leg_imu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://otaheri.github.io/publication/2019_leg_imu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;abstract&#34;&gt;Abstract&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Human motion capture is frequently used to study rehabilitation and clinical problems, as well
as to provide realistic animation for the entertainment industry. IMU-based systems, as well as Markerbased
motion tracking systems, are most popular methods to track movement due to their low cost of
implementation and lightweight. This paper proposes a quaternion-based Extended Kalman filter
approach to recover the human leg segments motions with a set of IMU sensors data fused with
cameramarker system data. In this paper, an Extended Kalman Filter approach is developed to fuse the data of
two IMUs and one RGB camera for human leg motion tracking. Based on the complementary properties
of the inertial sensors and camera-marker system, in the introduced new measurement model, the
orientation data of the upper leg and the lower leg is updated through three measurement equations. The
positioning of the human body is made possible by the tracked position of the pelvis joint by the camera
marker system. A mathematical model has been utilized to estimate joints’ depth in 2D images. The
efficiency of the proposed algorithm is evaluated by an optical motion tracker system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;!--
# Video

&lt;div style=&#34;text-align:center;&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://download.is.tue.mpg.de/arctic/video.mp4&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


# Data and Code

Please register and accept the License agreement on [GRAB](https://grab.is.tue.mpg.de) website in order to get access to the GRAB dataset. 



# Citation

```

```
--&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
